Well...
这个...
I fear I told a little fib
我撒了小小一个谎
About my pony past
没讲过去真相
I hope that when you hear the truth
但愿你听到实情后
You will not be aghast
不会太过惊慌
I wasn't quite the super party pony like I claimed
其实我原本并非什么派对大明星
The fact is that I was so shy
没有谁记得我名字 因为我太内向
Nopony knew my-y name
I stumbled into Ponyville
那天下午我偶然来到了小马镇上
One afternoon by chance
And found the biggest ever celebration party dance
一场盛大的庆祝派对就在那广场
Everything was perfect
一切多么完美
Cheer was filling up the place
欢声四处在飘荡
And I saw that everypony had
还有微笑挂在每匹小马的脸上
A smile upon their face
I vowed that day to change my life
从此我立志在心里
The past I did set free
把过去全抛弃
For now Cheese Sandwich was
如今我起司三明治满心快乐活力
A party pony full of glee
A super duper party pony
我成了派对上的明星
That's what I became
实现了愿望
I traveled all Equestria
我跑遍了南北东西
And all did know my name
让名声扬四方
But that never would have happened on my own
如果不是那场派对 我难有今天成绩
I'll tell you why
For the one who threw that party
而那场派对的策划
It was you, Pinkie Pie
全亏有你萍琪
Me?
我?
Yes!
对!
Hah, really?
真的？
Really!
真的!
So I was the pony that threw the awesomely spectacular party
原来是我开了那个超级赞的大派对
that inspired you to become
然后你才立志成为了不起的派对主持？
an awesome spectacular party thrower?
Swear on Camembert!
就是这样！
Enough with the warm fuzzy stuff, you two
你俩就先别叙旧了好吗
It's my birth-iversary,
我的庆生会还等着你俩来开呢
and you gotta throw me a bash!
Yeah!
耶！
Let's go!
一起来!
Super duper party ponies --
最棒的派对小马
--that is me and you
是我也是你
A party thrown by one is good,
独自筹办虽可以
but not as great as two
但一起更惬意
Come on and let's join forces,
你和我互帮互助
have twice the expertise
投入两倍努力
Now let's all go to the party planned by Pinkie Pie and Cheese!
大家同乐的派对有我起司和萍琪